{"animal":[{"level":"1","type":"animal","question":"I quack and waddle. I like to swim in a puddle. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐥 I am a bird."},{"text":"🌾 I eat seeds and bread."},{"text":"💦 I like to play in water."}],"options":[{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"2","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Moo!' and give you milk. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"⚫ I have black and white spots."},{"text":"🌱 I eat grass."},{"text":"🥛 You can drink what I give."}],"options":[{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"3","type":"animal","question":"I bark and wag my tail. I love to play fetch. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦴 I love bones."},{"text":"🏠 I protect your house."},{"text":"🎾 I like to chase balls."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"4","type":"animal","question":"I purr and like to cuddle. I chase mice and play with string. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🧶 I like playing with yarn"},{"text":"🐟 I like to eat fish."},{"text":"🌙 I sleep a lot."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"5","type":"animal","question":"I have a long trunk and big ears. I never forget. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥜 I love peanuts."},{"text":"🐘 I am big and gray."},{"text":"🚿 I use my trunk as a hose."}],"options":[{"label":"Giraffe","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"6","type":"animal","question":"I swing from trees and love bananas. Who am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐒 I live in the jungle"},{"text":"🍌 I like a particular yellow fruit."},{"text":"🙊 I like to imitate people"}],"options":[{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Snake","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"7","type":"animal","question":"I have a long neck and eat leaves from tall trees. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦒 I am very tall."},{"text":"🌿 I eat leaves."},{"text":"I have brown spots"}],"options":[{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Giraffe","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Hippo","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"8","type":"animal","question":"I have black and white stripes and live in Africa. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦓 I have stripes all over my body."},{"text":"🌍 I live in the wild."},{"text":"🐎 I look like a horse."}],"options":[{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Leopard","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"9","type":"animal","question":"I slither on the ground and sometimes hiss. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐍 I have no legs."},{"text":"☀️ I like warm places."},{"text":"🐭 I sometimes eat mice."}],"options":[{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Snake","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Worm","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"10","type":"animal","question":"I roar and I'm known as the king of the jungle. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"👑 I have a mane."},{"text":"🦁 I am a big cat."},{"text":"🍖 I eat meat."}],"options":[{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}}],"food":[{"level":"1","type":"food","question":"I am yellow and you peel me before you eat me. Monkeys love me! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"📏 I am long and curved."},{"text":"🐒 I grow on trees in warm places."},{"text":"🟡 My color is the same as the sun."}],"options":[{"label":"Banana","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Apple","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Orange","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"2","type":"food","question":"I am round and red, and I keep the doctor away. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌳 I grow on trees."},{"text":"🌱 People say eating me is healthy."},{"text":"🟥 I am often the color of fire trucks."}],"options":[{"label":"Strawberry","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Apple","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Grape","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"3","type":"food","question":"I am white and come from a cow. You can drink me! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 I am often poured on cereal."},{"text":"🐄 Cows make me."},{"text":"🦴 I help make your bones strong."}],"options":[{"label":"Juice","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Milk","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Water","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"4","type":"food","question":"I am long and orange, and rabbits love to eat me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥕 I grow underground."},{"text":"🐇 Bugs Bunny eats me all the time."},{"text":"🔶 My color is similar to a pumpkin."}],"options":[{"label":"Carrot","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Potato","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Radish","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"5","type":"food","question":"I am small and green and grow in a pod. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🟢 I am the color of grass."},{"text":"🥣 I'm often eaten with a spoon."},{"text":"👪 I often grow with my friends in a little house."}],"options":[{"label":"Pea","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bean","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Broccoli","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"6","type":"food","question":"I am made from wheat and baked in an oven. You can make sandwiches with me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍞 I am often sliced."},{"text":"🌾 I am made from a grain."},{"text":"🥪 You can put peanut butter and jelly on me."}],"options":[{"label":"Rice","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bread","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pasta","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"7","type":"food","question":"I am orange and juicy. People drink me for breakfast. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍊 I am a citrus fruit."},{"text":"☀️ I'm often enjoyed in the morning."},{"text":"🥤 You can drink my juice."}],"options":[{"label":"Lemon","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Orange","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Grapefruit","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"8","type":"food","question":"I am made from potatoes, and I am crispy and salty. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍟 I am often served with ketchup."},{"text":"🥔 I start as a root vegetable."},{"text":"🧂 People like to add salt to me."}],"options":[{"label":"French Fries","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Mashed Potatoes","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Potato Salad","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"9","type":"food","question":"I am round and covered in seeds. I can be red, green, or yellow. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍉 I am often eaten in the summer."},{"text":"🌱 I grow on a vine."},{"text":"⚫ My seeds can be black or white."}],"options":[{"label":"Tomato","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Watermelon","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cantaloupe","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"10","type":"food","question":"I am a treat that's cold and sweet. I come in many flavors, and you eat me with a spoon. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍦 I can be in a cone."},{"text":"🍓 I am often flavored with fruit or chocolate."},{"text":"🥶 You need to keep me in the freezer."}],"options":[{"label":"Cake","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Ice Cream","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cookie","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}}]}